<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voice of Fider Developers on Fider</title>
    <link>https://getfider.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voice of Fider Developers on Fider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://getfider.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.18 has been released with attachments and better SEO</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.18.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.18.0/</guid>
      <description>#1: Image Attachments This is the third version in a row that we have delivered our most wanted feature, which in this version was Image Attachments on Posts and Comments 🎉
This new feature that allows users to upload up to 3 images when submitting a new post or comment.
Staff members still have full control over the post/comment and can delete or replace any uploaded image.
  #2: Better SEO (experimental) For those who are new to Fider, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know that Fider is a client-side rendered application built with React.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.17 has been released with list of voters, better user management and huge performance improvements</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.17.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.17.0/</guid>
      <description>#1: List of Voters Our most wanted feature has been implemented! 🎉
It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to see the list of everyone who voted on a given post. We&amp;rsquo;ve added another sidebar panel to the post, like the following:
  Staff members can drill down and see more information about everyone who voted on that post by clicking on +x more. Visitors doesn&amp;rsquo;t have this access because this includes private information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How we reduced our initial JS/CSS size by 67%</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/how-we-reduced-initial-jscss-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/how-we-reduced-initial-jscss-size/</guid>
      <description>Fider is built with React and Webpack on the frontend, so the topics below will be mostly useful for teams using same stack, but the concepts can also be applied to other stacks.
Table of Contents  Webpack Bundle Analyzer Long term caching with content hash The common bundle Code Splitting on route level Loading external dependencies on demand Font Awesome and Tree Shaking Switching from big to small NPM packages Optimising the main bundle is crucial TSLib (TypeScript only)  Webpack Bundle Analyzer webpack-bundle-analyzer is a webpack plugin that generates an interactive zoomable treemap of all your bundles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.16 released with Public API, delete comments and other improvements</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.16.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.16.0/</guid>
      <description>#1: Public API For a long time, the Public API has been the most wanted feature on Fider. We&amp;rsquo;re now happy to share that the API is live and ready to be used.
The Public API allows site owners to perform different actions via a programmatic interface. The API uses common web standards like REST, HTTP and JSON to make it easier for anyone to integrate with Fider. Visit the Official API documentation to learn more about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.15 released with custom OAuth and minor improvements</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.15.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.15.0/</guid>
      <description>In this release we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on authentication improvements for Fider. For a long time we have enabled visitors to sign in via Facebook, Google, GitHub and email, but that&amp;rsquo;s not enough. Custom providers was a highly requested feature so that we could have authentication via Twitch, Discord, Spotify, Azure AD, Strava and many many others.
#1: Custom OAuth From the Site Settings -&amp;gt; Authentication, Administrators are now able to configure authentication with any provider that supports OAuth2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.14 released with improved foundation and minor features</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.14.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.14.0/</guid>
      <description>In this release we&amp;rsquo;ve focused on technical improvements, but we managed to deliver minor features as well. This is a necessary step towards building a product that can be further enhanced with new features.
#1: Filter ideas that I voted We&amp;rsquo;ve included a new filter option: My Votes. This option will show all ideas that the current signed in user has already voted on. It is only available for signed in users</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.13 released with custom branding and legal compliance</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.13.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.13.0/</guid>
      <description>#1: Custom Branding First thing we&amp;rsquo;d like to highlight is that administratrors are now able to upload a logo for the site. This logo is shown on different places, like the Header, the error pages, favicon and also on social links. We highly recommend everyone to upload a company/product logo as this will result in a much nicer social sharing experience.
  The other big addition is the Custom CSS, which allows administrators to write their own CSS to change the design of nearly everything on the site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.12 released with features for privacy and export data</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.12.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.12.0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We&amp;rsquo;re super excited about this release! Private site was a highly requested feature that brings a lot of value in some particular situations. This feature open a range of possibilities on how people can leverage Fider on their projects and organizations.
Aside from that, we&amp;rsquo;re also shipping a built-in option to export all your ideas to a CSV. This can be particularly useful if you want to do some analysis on an external tool like Excel or any of your favorite Business Intelligence tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.11 released with option to edit and delete ideas</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.11.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.11.0/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s very well known that as the size of the codebase grows, so does the complexity and time needed to maintain it. This is a common characteristic of most software programs and thus, not different for Fider.
As we evolve one version a month we need to always look back and improve older code, even those small pieces that are still working sometimes needs some love. Refactoring older code to make it easier to read, maintain and change is something we&amp;rsquo;ll be doing more often moving forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.10 released with notifications system and more</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.10.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.10.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Web and Email Notifications This has been, for a long time, the most wanted feature of Fider. The notification system is based on a subscription model where users are only notified about ideas they subscribed to. This can be done manually by clicking on &amp;ldquo;Subscribe&amp;rdquo; or automatically whenever they vote or comment on it.
As for Collaborators and Administrators, they automatically subscribe to all ideas, although it&amp;rsquo;s possible to unsubscribe from each idea individually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.9 released with features to merge duplicate ideas, sort by trending ideas and more</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.9.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.9.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Merge duplicate ideas It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to mark an idea as a Duplicate of another idea. This is particular useful to clean up the ideas list when someone shares an idea that has already been posted before.
When an idea is marked as a duplicate, it will show a link to the original idea and all its votes will be added to it as well.
  2. Sort by trending Fider now shows trending ideas by default instead of recent ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.8 released with tags and edit posts feature</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.8.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.8.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Assign tag to posts Our recent most wanted feature has been implemented. Starting from this release, administrators are able to create tags and assign tags to posts.
  Tags can be either Public or Private. Private tags are especially helpful for administrators to organize their posts without leaking any information publicly.
Tags can also be used to filter posts, alongside with the new free text search box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.7 released with members administration and automatic SSL</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.7.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Add/Remove Members This feature has been suggested during the month and received a few votes on a short amount of time. This is a really basic feature that we were missing and now we&amp;rsquo;re happy to ship the first version of it on this release.
  2. Technical Improvements This release was all about Technical Improvements. We&amp;rsquo;ve removed echo, updated React to v16, increased code coverage, removed other dependencies and refactored a lot of code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.6 released with sign in by email</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.6.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Sign in by email We heard more than once that required users to use their Social accounts to sign in is not the way to go. Some people might not have these accounts or don&amp;rsquo;t want to link they because of privacy concerns, which is totally understandable!
With this in mind, we are happy to release v0.6.0 with a very simple sign in by email process. There&amp;rsquo;s no need for users to fill in any form, all they need to do is type their email and click on the link that we send.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.5 released with a great redesign and GitHub authentication</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.5.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Redesign The goal of this redesign was a default theme that could be easily used any customer, without forcing the violet theme. We&amp;rsquo;ve also removed the focus from the vote counter to the content, while keeping it simple and clean.
 Fider 0.4.0   Fider 0.5.0  2. Staff highlight Staff members will now have a different color on their names on discussions.
  3. Login with GitHub GitHub is the world&amp;rsquo;s leading software development platform and now we allow users to log in using their GitHub profiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.4 released with markdown and customizable text</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.4.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Redesign The home page has been redesigned to make better use of the large screens on desktops, while keeping it clean and simple on mobile and tablets.
 Fider 0.3.0   Fider 0.4.0  2. Ideas filter While on home page you&amp;rsquo;ll now be able to filter and sort ideas based on commonly used criteria.
This will help you quickly find most wanted ideas and those that are currently trending!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider 0.3 released with staff response, SSL and sign up process</title>
      <link>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://getfider.com/blog/version-0.3.0/</guid>
      <description>1. Staff now can add official response to ideas In you&amp;rsquo;re part of the Staff of a tenant, you&amp;rsquo;ll now see a Respond button where you can give your official status on what&amp;rsquo;s the plan for that idea. As of now, we&amp;rsquo;re currently supporting the following status: New, Started, Completed and Declined.
  2. Much simpler Sign up / Installation process On previous versions, installing a new Fider instance required some SQL commands to be run.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>