<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Feedback. Get Fider. on Fider</title>
    <link>http://getfider.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Get Feedback. Get Fider. on Fider</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://getfider.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your own instance</title>
      <link>http://getfider.com/docs/hosting-instance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getfider.com/docs/hosting-instance/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites We highly recommend using Docker to host the application. It&#39;s the easiest and fastest way to get started and stay up to date with any future release.
You&#39;ll also need a Postgres 9.6+ database, which could also be hosted on Docker, but that&#39;s not required.
Installing and Running Step 1: Create a docker compose file  Create a file named docker-compose.yml and copy content below. Read comments for to know what settings are available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider v0.4.0 Released</title>
      <link>http://getfider.com/blog/version-0.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getfider.com/blog/version-0.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Fider v0.4.0 has just been released and includes following features:
1. Redesign The home page has been redesigned to make better use of the large screens on desktops, while keeping it clean and simple on mobile and tablets.
 Fider 0.3.0   Fider 0.4.0  2. Ideas filter While on home page you&amp;rsquo;ll now be able to filter and sort ideas based on commonly used criterias.
This will help you quickly find mosted wanted ideas and those that are currently trending!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fider v0.3.0 Released</title>
      <link>http://getfider.com/blog/version-0.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getfider.com/blog/version-0.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Fider v0.3.0 has just been released and includes following features:
1. Staff now can add official response to ideas In you&amp;rsquo;re part of the Staff of a tenant, you&amp;rsquo;ll now see a Respond button where you can give your official status on what&amp;rsquo;s the plan for that idea. As of now, we&amp;rsquo;re currently supporting the following status: New, Started, Completed and Declined.
  2. Much simpler Sign up / Installation process On previous versions, installing a new Fider instance required some SQL commands to be run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuring OAuth</title>
      <link>http://getfider.com/docs/configuring-oauth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getfider.com/docs/configuring-oauth/</guid>
      <description>Why is this required? Authentication is a key component of Fider platform. We take security and usability very seriously, which is why we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to go with Social sign in as the main authentication method. If you&amp;rsquo;ve just got started with Fider, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Facebook and/or a Google app to get authentication to work.
But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, it&amp;rsquo;s a very easy and fast setup explained below.
Facebook Pending&amp;hellip; https://developers.facebook.com/apps/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to enable SSL</title>
      <link>http://getfider.com/docs/how-to-enable-ssl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://getfider.com/docs/how-to-enable-ssl/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites In order to configure HTTPS, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Certificate and the Private Key.
How to enable it Fider v0.3.0 shipped with two new environment variables that you&amp;rsquo;ll need to set.
 SSL_CERT: This is the path to the Certificate file. SSL_CERT_KEY: This is the path to the Private Key file.  If you&amp;rsquo;re using Docker, these files won&amp;rsquo;t be inside the container, but Fider will need to have access to it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>